model3ownersclub.com 2018-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Tesla Model 3 Owners Club

__

**Tesla Model 3 Owners Club**

[__](https://model3ownersclub.com/)__ Help __

**Privacy Policy**

Model 3 Owners Club (M3OC) is fully committed to protecting the privacy of our users. The M3OC privacy policy applies to Model3OwnersClub.com and addresses the manner in which we deal with data collection and usage of that data. Though we do our best to follow the policies listed below, we cannot be held responsible for compromised privacy and the damage that it may cause, or make guarantees of privacy, due to forces and elements outside of M3OC’s control. 

**Personal Data Collection**

M3OC collects specific user information, including but not limited to, email addresses, names and locations. M3OC also collects information pertaining to users’ computer hardware and software. This includes IP address, OS (and its version), internet provider, device being used, language, general location(as specific as city), and user access times,durations and engagement. For the purpose of M3OC events, such as M3OC Connect, M3OC collects other information, including but not limited to, address, phone number, emergency contact information and EV ownership details. This information is used by M3OC to better tailor the M3OC website and M3OC events for our users and also to maintain data on the usage of Model3OwnersClub.com. 

Please be advised that any personal information that you make public on the M3OC forum or any other part of the Model3OwnersClub.com website, may be used and collected by others. M3OC is not responsible for any damage that may result from information being made public by a user. M3OC, at its own discretion, may choose to help a user by removing personal data that they, in error, made public. 

M3OC does not intentionally read any of the private communications made between M3OC users on the M3OC website however, from time to time, private messages may be witnessed by administrators of the service in the course of their normal activities. 

Please refer to the privacy statements of other websites that you link to on M3OC to find out how these other websites deal with your information. M3OC is not responsible for the privacy statements or content of other websites. 

**Use of Personal Information**

Personal data collected by M3OC, such as email addresses, are used primarily to contact users regarding important announcements such as notification of maintenance schedules. M3OC may occasionally notify you by email of new services and upgrades to the M3OC website, as well as let you know about our sponsors who we think may be of interest to you. You may unsubscribe to these messages at any point if you wish. 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting business, or servicing you, so long as those parties operate with M3OC’s permission and agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provide to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

We may on occasion contact you regarding offering from our sponsors that we believe may be of interest to you. In those particular cases, we will not share any personal data to those sponsors(third parties). 

M3OC may share anonymous usage data with sponsors in order to help them understand the demographics of M3OC users. 

M3OC may also, in good faith, find it necessary to disclose personal information in order: a) to conform to the law or comply with legal process served on M3OC; b) protect and defend the rights or property of M3OC; and c) to act under necessary circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of M3OC or the public. 

In order to keep your personal information, messages and accounts secure, we keep the Model3OwnersClub.com data on servers which are located in a safe and secure environment. The servers are protected from unauthorized access and use. We take all basic reasonable measures to keep our and your data secure, however we live in a world where many hackers manage to break into even the most secure websites, and therefore we cannot be held accountable for the nefarious actions of such a third party. 

**Future Changes to Privacy Policy**

As M3OC is a growing and developing website and community, we may, from time to time, need to adjust and modify the Privacy Policy to cover some of the changes and additions we may do to the website. If you are concerned about your privacy, we suggest you recheck the privacy policy from time to time. If there are significant changes, we may make an effort to inform the M3OC community by forum or blog post, or by email. 

**Cookies**

The forum software uses cookies to maintain session state and authentication state for users. The advertising platform and social network links may or may not use cookies as defined by their respective privacy policies. Use of this site implies acceptance of this and their use of cookies. 

**Contact**

If you feel at all that we at M3OC are not upholding correctly to our privacy policy, please do let us know via the Contact Us link at the bottom of the page. We will do our best to address your concern right away.
